In a live broadcast on Al Jazeera Arabic Wednesday, Gaza bureau chief Wa'el Dadu learned
his wife, daughter and son had been killed in an Israeli airstrike.
Dadu's grandson, a toddler, was pronounced dead just hours later, all of them killed
by a missile that flattened a home where the family had been sheltering from Israel's
round-the-clock bombardment.
Another of Dadu's sons was seriously injured with a head wound.
The family had fled Israel's bombardment of their neighborhood in the north to seek
shelter in the Nusrat refugee camp in Central Gaza, heeding Israel's order to 1.1 million
Palestinians to evacuate southwards.
It can be that the land of the land, and that we already know, that even Hamas doesn't
know, it can be that there was a threat, and they still don't know what's going on, and
they also don't know what's going on, and it's true for many places in Gaza.
We know the goal, for example, today was the goal of the land of Al Jazeera, but we know
that in places that we don't know, then we're looking for the details of Hamas.
Days since the evacuation order, not one day, not one hour, these places were not targeted.
Homes were targeted, hospitals were targeted.
In these same areas that people were asked to evacuate, hundreds of families who had evacuated
from the north and from Gaza City were killed in those bombings.
When we say there's no safe place in Gaza, we're not lying, we're not being biased, we're
not exaggerating.
The north, Gaza City, and the south, they're all just the same.
They're all just the same.